{
    "id": "plumery-gear",
    "type": "Gear",
    "name": "Plumery Gear",
    "cards": [
        {
            "id": "arc-bow",
            "type": "gear",
            "name": "Arc Bow",
            "front": "arc-bow.webp",
            "back": "_back.webp",
            "keywords": [
                "weapon",
                "ranged",
                "bow",
                "two-handed"
            ],
            "speed": 1,
            "accuracy": 6,
            "strength": 9,
            "rules": [
                "Slow",
                "Range 6"
            ],
            "desc": "<b>Cumbersome:</b> Spend <font class=\"kdm_font\">c</font> as an additional cost of activating this weapon.",
            "affinities": {
                "left": "red",
                "right": "green"
            },
            "affinity_bonus": {
                "desc": "Range +2",
                "requires": {
                    "puzzle": {
                        "red": 1,
                        "green": 1
                    },
                    "complete": {
                        "blue": 1
                    }
                }
            },
            "sub_type": "plumery",
            "type_pretty": "Gear",
            "sub_type_pretty": "Plumery",
            "selector_text": "Arc Bow",
            "handle": "arc_bow"
        },
        {
            "id": "bird-bread",
            "type": "gear",
            "name": "Bird Bread",
            "front": "bird-bread.webp",
            "back": "_back.webp",
            "keywords": [
                "item",
                "consumable",
                "soluble"
            ],
            "affinities": {
                "right": "green"
            },
            "desc": "<font class=\"kdm_font\">a</font> <b>Consume:</b> Once per showdown, add <font class=\"inline_shield\">1</font> to all hit locations. Gain <b>priority target</b> token. Roll 1d10. On a 1, reduce your survival to 0.",
            "sub_type": "plumery",
            "type_pretty": "Gear",
            "sub_type_pretty": "Plumery",
            "selector_text": "Bird Bread",
            "handle": "bird_bread",
            "rules": []
        },
        {
            "id": "bloom-sphere",
            "type": "gear",
            "name": "Bloom Sphere",
            "front": "bloom-sphere.webp",
            "back": "_back.webp",
            "keywords": [
                "item",
                "stinky",
                "other"
            ],
            "affinities": {
                "left": "green",
                "right": "blue"
            },
            "affinity_bonus": {
                "desc": "When you are picked as a target, roll 1d10. On a 6+, the monster must pick a new target, if possible.",
                "requires": {
                    "puzzle": {
                        "green": 1,
                        "blue": 1
                    }
                }
            },
            "sub_type": "plumery",
            "type_pretty": "Gear",
            "sub_type_pretty": "Plumery",
            "selector_text": "Bloom Sphere",
            "handle": "bloom_sphere",
            "rules": [],
            "desc": ""
        },
        {
            "id": "crest-crown",
            "type": "gear",
            "name": "Crest Crown",
            "front": "crest-crown.webp",
            "back": "_back.webp",
            "keywords": [
                "item",
                "other"
            ],
            "affinities": {
                "top": "blue",
                "left": "red",
                "right": "green",
                "bottom": "blue"
            },
            "desc": "<font class=\"kdm_font\">a</font>: If <b>insane</b>, reshuffle hit location deck.",
            "affinity_bonus": {
                "desc": "When you depart, gain +1 insanity and +1 survival for every <font class=\"kdm_font_2 affinity_blue_text\">h</font> you have.",
                "requires": {
                    "puzzle": {
                        "red": 1,
                        "blue": 2
                    }
                }
            },
            "sub_type": "plumery",
            "type_pretty": "Gear",
            "sub_type_pretty": "Plumery",
            "selector_text": "Crest Crown",
            "handle": "crest_crown",
            "rules": []
        },
        {
            "id": "feather-mantle",
            "type": "gear",
            "name": "Feather Mantle",
            "front": "feather-mantle.webp",
            "back": "_back.webp",
            "keywords": [
                "item",
                "flammable"
            ],
            "affinities": {
                "left": "blue",
                "right": "green",
                "bottom": "red"
            },
            "desc": "When you suffer <b>knockback</b>, you may ignore <b>collision</b> with other survivors and reduce movement by up to 3 spaces.",
            "sub_type": "plumery",
            "type_pretty": "Gear",
            "sub_type_pretty": "Plumery",
            "selector_text": "Feather Mantle",
            "handle": "feather_mantle",
            "rules": []
        },
        {
            "id": "feather-shield",
            "type": "gear",
            "name": "Feather Shield",
            "front": "feather-shield.webp",
            "back": "_back.webp",
            "keywords": [
                "weapon",
                "melee",
                "shield",
                "flammable"
            ],
            "speed": 3,
            "accuracy": 7,
            "strength": 0,
            "rules": [
                "Block 1"
            ],
            "affinities": {
                "top": "blue"
            },
            "affinity_bonus": {
                "desc": "Reduce any suffered brain damage by 1 to a minimum of 1.",
                "requires": {
                    "complete": {
                        "red": 1,
                        "blue": 1,
                        "green": 1
                    }
                }
            },
            "sub_type": "plumery",
            "type_pretty": "Gear",
            "sub_type_pretty": "Plumery",
            "selector_text": "Feather Shield",
            "handle": "feather_shield",
            "desc": ""
        },
        {
            "id": "hollow-sword",
            "type": "gear",
            "name": "Hollow Sword",
            "front": "hollow-sword.webp",
            "back": "_back.webp",
            "keywords": [
                "weapon",
                "melee",
                "sword",
                "bone"
            ],
            "speed": 3,
            "accuracy": 5,
            "strength": 3,
            "rules": [
                "Frail",
                "Paired"
            ],
            "desc": "On a <b>perfect hit</b>, make 1 additional attack roll.",
            "sub_type": "plumery",
            "type_pretty": "Gear",
            "sub_type_pretty": "Plumery",
            "selector_text": "Hollow Sword",
            "handle": "hollow_sword"
        },
        {
            "id": "hollowpoint-arrow",
            "type": "gear",
            "name": "Hollowpoint Arrow",
            "front": "hollowpoint-arrow.webp",
            "back": "_back.webp",
            "keywords": [
                "item",
                "ammunition",
                "arrow"
            ],
            "speed": 1,
            "accuracy": 6,
            "strength": 11,
            "rules": [
                "Slow",
                "Ammo - Bow"
            ],
            "desc": "On a hit, monster gains -1 movement token. Use once per showdown.",
            "sub_type": "plumery",
            "type_pretty": "Gear",
            "sub_type_pretty": "Plumery",
            "selector_text": "Hollowpoint Arrow",
            "handle": "hollowpoint_arrow"
        },
        {
            "id": "hours-ring",
            "type": "gear",
            "name": "Hours Ring",
            "front": "hours-ring.webp",
            "back": "_back.webp",
            "keywords": [
                "item",
                "other"
            ],
            "rules": [
                "Unique",
                "Selfish"
            ],
            "desc": "Do not gain any tokens for any reason. Do not gain Hunt XP or weapon proficiency. <b>Retired</b> wearers can <b>depart</b>.",
            "sub_type": "plumery",
            "type_pretty": "Gear",
            "sub_type_pretty": "Plumery",
            "selector_text": "Hours Ring",
            "handle": "hours_ring"
        },
        {
            "id": "phoenix-faulds",
            "type": "gear",
            "name": "Phoenix Faulds",
            "front": "phoenix-faulds.webp",
            "back": "_back.webp",
            "keywords": [
                "armor",
                "set",
                "feather",
                "metal",
                "flammable"
            ],
            "armor": 4,
            "location": "waist",
            "desc": "When you <b>depart</b>, gain +1 insanity.",
            "sub_type": "plumery",
            "type_pretty": "Gear",
            "sub_type_pretty": "Plumery",
            "selector_text": "Phoenix Faulds",
            "handle": "phoenix_faulds",
            "rules": []
        },
        {
            "id": "phoenix-gauntlet",
            "type": "gear",
            "name": "Phoenix Gauntlet",
            "front": "phoenix-gauntlet.webp",
            "back": "_back.webp",
            "armor": 4,
            "location": "arms",
            "keywords": [
                "armor",
                "set",
                "feather",
                "metal",
                "flammable"
            ],
            "desc": "When you <b>depart</b>, gain +1 insanity.",
            "sub_type": "plumery",
            "type_pretty": "Gear",
            "sub_type_pretty": "Plumery",
            "selector_text": "Phoenix Gauntlet",
            "handle": "phoenix_gauntlet",
            "rules": []
        },
        {
            "id": "phoenix-greaves",
            "type": "gear",
            "name": "Phoenix Greaves",
            "front": "phoenix-greaves.webp",
            "back": "_back.webp",
            "keywords": [
                "armor",
                "set",
                "feather",
                "metal",
                "flammable"
            ],
            "affinities": {
                "right": "red"
            },
            "armor": 4,
            "location": "legs",
            "desc": "If <b>insane</b>, gain +2 movement.",
            "sub_type": "plumery",
            "type_pretty": "Gear",
            "sub_type_pretty": "Plumery",
            "selector_text": "Phoenix Greaves",
            "handle": "phoenix_greaves",
            "rules": []
        },
        {
            "id": "phoenix-helm",
            "type": "gear",
            "name": "Phoenix Helm",
            "front": "phoenix-helm.webp",
            "back": "_back.webp",
            "keywords": [
                "armor",
                "set",
                "feather",
                "metal",
                "flammable"
            ],
            "armor": 4,
            "location": "head",
            "affinities": {
                "bottom": "blue"
            },
            "affinity_bonus": {
                "desc": "If <b>insane</b> at the start of the showdown, gain +1 evasion token.",
                "requires": {
                    "puzzle": {
                        "blue": 1
                    },
                    "complete": {
                        "green": 1,
                        "red": 1
                    }
                }
            },
            "sub_type": "plumery",
            "type_pretty": "Gear",
            "sub_type_pretty": "Plumery",
            "selector_text": "Phoenix Helm",
            "handle": "phoenix_helm",
            "rules": [],
            "desc": ""
        },
        {
            "id": "phoenix-plackart",
            "type": "gear",
            "name": "Phoenix Plackart",
            "front": "phoenix-plackart.webp",
            "back": "_back.webp",
            "keywords": [
                "armor",
                "set",
                "feather",
                "metal",
                "flammable"
            ],
            "location": "body",
            "armor": 4,
            "affinities": {
                "top": "blue",
                "left": "green",
                "right": "red"
            },
            "affinity_bonus": {
                "desc": "If <b>insane</b>, ignore the first hit each round and suffer 1 brain damage instead.",
                "requires": {
                    "puzzle": {
                        "red": 1,
                        "blue": 1,
                        "green": 1
                    }
                }
            },
            "sub_type": "plumery",
            "type_pretty": "Gear",
            "sub_type_pretty": "Plumery",
            "selector_text": "Phoenix Plackart",
            "handle": "phoenix_plackart",
            "rules": [],
            "desc": ""
        },
        {
            "id": "sonic-tomahawk",
            "type": "gear",
            "name": "Sonic Tomahawk",
            "front": "sonic-tomahawk.webp",
            "back": "_back.webp",
            "speed": 3,
            "accuracy": 5,
            "strength": 2,
            "affinities": {
                "left": "red"
            },
            "keywords": [
                "weapon",
                "melee",
                "axe",
                "metal"
            ],
            "desc": "On a <b>perfect hit</b>, make 1 additional attack roll.",
            "affinity_bonus": {
                "desc": "Gain <b>Savage</b> and <b>Paired</b>",
                "requires": {
                    "puzzle": {
                        "red": 1
                    },
                    "complete": {
                        "green": 2,
                        "blue": 1
                    }
                }
            },
            "sub_type": "plumery",
            "type_pretty": "Gear",
            "sub_type_pretty": "Plumery",
            "selector_text": "Sonic Tomahawk",
            "handle": "sonic_tomahawk",
            "rules": []
        }
    ]
}